cards laid out the show. Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold. There's magic in her hands, whisper what the future holds. Dance to the mystery, yeah, yeah, yeah. So, let the tarot move with the rhythm.
Thank you for being here. Oh my god. That's not good. You got the gardener is working outside. I'm sorry
I had to close my door. I'll be right back.
stream neon eyes and conspiracy dreams talking cults in the desert sand
tattoo maps and shaking hands she's got screenshots names and days a tin for
halo ceiling fades in a chaff room chapel saints confess every broadcast feels
like a hole
Might be right, dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbol of sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crazy clothes, gang, some traffickers
Crystals live with the digital saboteurs
Truth or fiction doesn't matter
So she's part oracle, part in a net myth, half the room's scared
The rest subsist, her eyeliner sharp as a truth dissected
And everything relieves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in
Because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin
Yeah, Crystal Marie.
Have you seen Crystal Marie, by the way, guys?
If you have seen her, just let her know my new channel.
You need to just found my new channel is Nick Johnson.
He didn't know.
He didn't know I had resurrected the cult
under a different channel.
I guess the old cult was sacrificed to the dark gods,
but it re-rows like the Phoenix, right?
And here I am.
Still here still streaming still queer
Get used to it
Not going anywhere. Also if you are
You ever do find yourself you can't find my channel I
You know who knows what happened on YouTube, but you can always go to cult of psyche calm
Then go to like live stream and you'll see like a schedule and you'll see like that
It'll be actually like live streaming there, too
Because I'm live streaming on kick at the same time. Yeah, so we're still here everything. Everything's okay. I
Think I think I think everything's okay. Hi, mr. John. Thank you
Yeah, if you can help me up with kick anybody can help with it. Oh my gosh. I had a good sleep
Miss me. Happy Halloween. Oh, hey, what's up? It's a Nick. Yeah. Oh, I'm on you and stuff
Hey, freeside. How are you? Hey everybody? Thanks for coming. Thanks for coming to the new channel. Yeah, miss you Halloween
I didn't really do that much of a Halloween. It was kind of like I'm not that great of a Halloween, right?
I think this happened. I got my channel deleted on the October 30th. It was back October 30th
And I was on Halloween night, but it wasn't like the big celebration. I wouldn't have liked but
It's okay
Long as I'm still here
Yeah, we do have haters
You know, I don't know what it was. I just read an article about YouTube and said I need to turn my notion on so I can
My notes taken from the show
Yeah, well apparently
The AI like there's a guy that had a channel with
350,000 subscribers
uh-huh 350,000 subscribers I had one or 2,700 right it's not you know so this
person has about like you know 15 times more subscribers than me and YouTube to
start taking on all his channels like because of the because not if he was
using AI because you YouTube uses an AI to like detect stuff right meeting notes
Now we're just now we're transcribing
Okay, I
Know I saw that I saw that I didn't I didn't know what she was talking about
I don't know. I think she might have thought you were LD or something and not KZ or something, right?
She might have been confused. I'm not sure
And I've heard that story in context with somebody else, but I'm not I'm not even sure if it's numbers. I don't know
I got my McDonald's coffee
Let me fix my green screen. Hold on big like that. I can put that on
Okay
Gosh
But I had weird dreams. Okay, one of the dreams. I was at this like weird event
Oh, it's like with my family and it was like I kept like getting lost from them
Oh, I think it started getting weird.
Okay, so what happened was we left and on the way home,
like the car went over the bridge and we were like,
and all our cell phones still worked, like in the water,
they're underwater and stuff,
but they still worked miraculously for some reason.
Now I was able to call,
we were able to get to shore and so I survived.
I mean, it was just, that was weird.
Let me see visual effects, let me get my green screen.
Here I'll go into my beach or I'll just make the whole thing a beach. Well, I'll do that. There we go. Okay
Oh, and they said turning dreams and dreams I don't know. I
Don't know it was Casey. It's kind of weird, huh?
So, I don't you know, there's like
literally thousands of hours of my show.
I know there's porn bombs that were just like
unhidden accidentally that I did
because I unhitted like some old videos
and I would come across porn bombs and stuff.
Tell your story.
I can, let me see.
KZ wants to be cleared, so I'll just try to clear him.
Let me see.
Think I'm cagged into post.
Let me see KZ, yeah.
Okay, here's like the here's the thing he's talking about how I do it share screen. I'm not I'm a little bit
I'm a little bit the short I know I know let me see how do I how do I share it share screen entire screen
Allow okay, then I can pull it up here
Let me see if they're good.
Oh, yeah, here it is.
Do you see it?
Isn't that like a trend for a while?
I'm repeating, I'm doing that.
Maybe it's like,
it's like I see an apricot or something.
Let me talk a little bit about that, please.
Thank you guys, Natty.
It was not being used to me.
Yeah, I heard about that song. Sorry, I didn't hear it.
That's KZ.
No, I can't see. I think somebody...
He doesn't know.
I don't know. I'm thinking.
I said what is that I said the last thing I said I said wasn't that the trend that really we're doing
Okay, I mean, I don't know how much that I'm dead that that clears things up, but I don't know I think she was confused I
Played it I played it. Come on. I played it
There okay, let's take a look. Okay. It's okay. I can even understand. Okay, so how are we doing guys?
Yeah, we're on the beach
Yeah, I hope but hopefully some good people fall be over here. Let's do a let's do a collective read
We can do a reading
For the channel, maybe hope it comes with the tower, of course, you know
You know, we just had a tower, but
Okay, what we got that king of wands victory at all costs maybe that was me a little bit
It's the victory at all costs king of wands
Sorry, there we go. That's a little better
King of wands victory at all costs. Maybe that was me. I was very passionate very very
Oh, I don't care what I mean. I don't care as long as I'm winning. Okay, but then look stab ten times in the back
Right
These were the porn bombs these were the people that were reporting the channel people that were just hate on the channel people that
I tried to take away from the
From the vibe of the channel
spreading
malicious gossip
Okay
True, but we have a cleaner cups too. We have a very generous good-hearted person. Okay
There we go your Alexander McQueen for Halloween
with a blow horn on TikTok?
Oh my God.
I wanna see a video of that if you can share.
But Queen of Cubs, that's also like,
also like the good heart of people that came back
that are still here, right?
You get the Wheel of Fortune.
That's actually going in my favor, right?
So maybe there wasn't such a bad thing.
Maybe there was some stuff that was like,
it'd rather happen, that happened then,
that happened like in the future, right?
But it's a timing
Collector I'm going back collecting old episodes collecting all I can all I can and try to
Try to salvage everything send me able to do salvaging the channel for pentacles to collector, right?
Night of pentacles someone's coming for me with good news, but financially, okay?
Financially or some kind of offer or something good. Maybe there's offers. I'll open up to have it
Hey, I noticed that my other channels probably shadow ban because I was getting like 40 people in the chat yesterday
And haven't got 40 people in quite a while in my main channel. Hey, Rudy
So, I thank you guys for coming back here to the channel. Why don't you come on up if you want to come on up?
Have a chat. I don't know how long I'll be on right now, but I
Do plan to
Come back later today. I'm sorry. I've been a little bit tired a little bit depressed a little bit out of it
Okay
There we go. There's a stream yard. Come on up
Restart in the show
This channel is actually doing pretty well, I don't know if I can remontage on this channel
I don't know. I don't know if they'll allow me that to do that or if it's allowed
I did not get three strikes and I'm out. I just got the channel deleted. So
It was kind of like a more I don't understand how it works. I thought it was always like the three strikes and you're out I
Didn't know that like you know good times and beta both had their channels taken down because of like a porn bomb
and
That they didn't get or that they put in on private or something or
So oh
There's almost to come up. If not, then I mean, maybe it's not good timing right now. It is a little quiet right here
I might play a couple songs and and
Let you guys go
No one's to
chill right now, but
I still I thank you for being here and
Supporting me. You're very appreciated. Okay
Let's see what we got going on
Glitch in the cathedral of code, flesh rebooted from the static
Memory dripping down the altar of my tongue
No lawyers here, no council, only echoes of the last timeline
Where we prayed to our screens and called it salvation
They still whisper, get my handler on the phone
Selling paid
Okay, so I guess I'll play. Oh, no, I'll show you my website.
Okay, you can see how it looks. It's not done, of course, but
let's have a look. Okay.
K-U-L-T-O-F-P-S-Y-C-H-E dot com
There we go, Arturo meets Twitch. Welcome to the Cult of Psyche, where mysticism meets the algorithm, and your third eye gets a Wi-Fi upgrade.
Okay, now look, look at all the cool things. You have a live stream.
And look, there I am, live, on my show, with the chat in there.
Chat is in there. Okay, more streams coming soon, so I'm going to have my...
Past dreams
Do all videos. Let me see. Oh, yeah, I'll take yeah, see I'll take you to Twitch and you can see everything
Every card kick everything I've done on kick
Okay, you can also become an initiate. Is that set up yet? Yeah memberships are set up
You have memberships
mailing lists
So you will never ever
be without a
Be without cult of psyche, right?
Okay
Working on it still working on it still it'll it'll be good. It'll be good
Everyone who's watching beta is there. Oh, RG. Okay. Well, I guess it means not a good time for me, but
It's beta talking about me at all I wonder
Um
Well, thanks for being here guys. I guess no one wants to come up. I'm not feeling well. I'm still
Kind of out of it right now, so let's see if I feel better later today. I love you guys
Okay
People to grift okay. Well everyone check out our G. I guess have a good day guys. I love you